glinks.net 2018-03-08

# Privacy Policy – GLinks

**Privacy Policy Disclosure**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which GLinks  
collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each,  
a “User”) of the http://www.glinks.net website (“Site”).  
This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered  
by the Site.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from  
Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or  
resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously.  
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they  
voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply  
personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from  
engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about  
Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification  
information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical  
information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating  
system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar  
information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User  
experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for  
record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. You can  
choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in  
your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact  
with our Site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to  
login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. You  
should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers  
for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions  
about how to opt-out of certain practices. Deleting cookies does not mean you  
are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings  
that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the  
advertisements, a new cookie will be added. If you wish to disable cookies, you  
may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information  
about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the  
browsers’ respective websites.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing  
practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access,  
alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username,  
password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification  
information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information  
not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and  
users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the  
purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that  
link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers,  
sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or  
links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices  
employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or  
services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These  
sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service  
policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites  
which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and  
policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by  
advertising partners, including Google and other ad networks, who may set  
cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time  
they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification  
information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows  
ad partners to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they  
believe will be of most interest to you. You may view the Google privacy  
policy at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/. This privacy policy does not  
cover the use of cookies by individual advertisers.

**Compliance with children’s online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially  
important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site  
from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is  
structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Changes to this privacy  
policy**  
We have the discretion to update this privacy policy at any  
time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page.  
We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay  
informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we  
collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review  
this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this  
policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your  
continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will  
be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the  
practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: [hugehuge4@gmail.com](mailto:hugehuge4@gmail.com) or [quantraxanh@gmail.com](mailto:quantraxanh@gmail.com)

This document was last updated on April 24, 2017
